<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
   <string name="app_name">Stress Management</string>
   <string name="wind_down">I found it hard to wind down</string>
   <string name="over_react">I tended to over-react to situations</string>
   <string name="nervous_energy">I felt that I was using a lot of nervous energy</string>
   <string name="agitated">I found myself getting agitated</string>
   <string name="relax">I found it difficult to relax</string>
   <string name="intolerant">I was intolerant of anything that kept me from getting on with what I was doing</string>
   <string name="touchy">I felt that I was rather touchy</string>
   <string name="not_applicable">Did not apply to me at all</string>
   <string name="some_degree">Applied to me to some degree, or some of the time</string>
   <string name="considerable_degree">Applied to me to a considerable degree, or a good part of time</string>
   <string name="high_degree">Applied to me very much, or most of the time</string>

   <string name="main_title">Live Stress Free</string>
   <string name="menu">Main Menu</string>
   <string name="results">Results</string>
   <string name="add_result">Result Entry</string>
   <string name="new_label">Stress Test</string>
   <string name="log_label">Stress Diary</string>
   <string name="return_label">Return to Main Menu</string>
   <string name="strategies_label">Self-care Plan</string>
   <string name="about_label">About</string>

   <string name="q1">1 of 7</string>
   <string name="q2">2 of 7</string>
   <string name="q3">3 of 7</string>
   <string name="q4">4 of 7</string>
   <string name="q5">5 of 7</string>
   <string name="q6">6 of 7</string>
   <string name="q7">7 of 7</string>

   <string name="about_text">
   This application is designed to help the user manage their stress levels
       through a feedback loop facilitated by the user\'s answers to a quiz. After determining your
       stress levels by taking the survey, use the stress diary to identify and record your stressors and symptoms.
       Then use the Self-Care plan to develop a plan of action for alleviating the affects of your
       stressors. Created for Software-Hardware Codesign course at FAU, spring 2016, Dr. Shankar.
       Created by Alex Achenbach and Dimitri DeBarnes, with input and consultation from
       Thisha Glover.
   </string>

    <string name="results_text">
       Normal: 0-14\n
       Mild: 15-18\n
       Moderate: 19-25\n
       Severe: 26-33\n
       Extremely Severe: 34+\n\n

       Based on the result of the user\'s answers and given the scale above, this page is where a specific recommendation
       will be given to the user telling them whether they are stressed or not, to what degree they are stressed, and what steps
       they can take to alleviate it.
   </string>

   <string name="sources">Stressors</string>
   <string name="symptoms">Symptoms of Stress</string>
   <string name="notes">Additional Notes</string>
   <string name="entry_text">

   Click on each category below (Stressors, Symptoms, and Additional Notes) to add some information about how you are feeling
       today. This information will be saved with your results from the previous page, so that you can get a sense of what
       your personal common stressors and symptoms are. This will allow you to create an action plan to lower your overall
       stress.

   </string>
    <string name="diary_button">Add Diary Entry</string>
    <string name="test_score_placeholder">Test Score</string>
    <string name="submit_to_diary">Submit Entry to Diary</string>
    <string name="textV_id">id</string>
    <string name="textV_date">date</string>
    <string name="textV_stress">stress</string>
    <string name="textV_sources">sources</string>
    <string name="textV_symptoms">symptoms</string>
    <string name="textV_notes">notes</string>


</resources>
